<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OutFits</string>


    <string name="mens_business_outfit">At home, you might still enjoy wearing those baggy shorts or oversized shirts even
        though you have slimmed down…

        \n\n\nBut outside, remember that fit is king. It’s your top concern in the style pyramid (before you think of
        fabric and function/style) for any clothing item.

        \n\n\nRule of thumb:
        \n\nIf it doesn’t fit (and can’t be slightly adjusted to fit) – do NOT buy it. It won’t work.
    </string>

    <string name="mens_casual_outfit">You want to dress better, but most style advice revolves around suiting up or just around whatever’s trendy
        this season. But that’s not what you’re looking for.

        \n\nYou just want to make a better first impression on people you meet in everyday life. You just want to look
        good in your clothes without looking too flashy.You just want to look like a better-dressed version of you.

        \n\nAnd that version of you still likes to keep it casual.

        \n\nSo what you’re really looking for is some casual style tips for guys who want to look sharp outside of a suit
        and tie. Well, you’ve come to the right place.
    </string>

    <string name="mens_modern_outfit">Don’t you agree these guys look much cooler and more masculine than the ones above? These kinda of t-shirts
        will make you stand out against an ocean of graphic-tee-wearing men.

        \n\n\nYou might also consider wearing polo shirts or casual shirts. Just because you’re dressing casual doesn’t
        mean you can’t wear a collar. And a simple white shirt looks great with a  pair of dark blue jeans, which
        I’ll cover in the next section of this list.
    </string>

    <string name="mens_street_outfit">These jeans won’t just look better, but they’re more versatile. Just look at these examples below and see
        how easily they can be dressed up and down as you see fit.

        \n\n\nNote: I’m not saying never, ever wear faded jeans, ever. While you should definitely have a straight
        dark-blue pair of jeans as pictured, you can certainly wear jeans with a subtle bit of fading. Just avoid
        those that are overly embellished.
    </string>


    <string name="womens_business_outfit">Pants are fine, but stick to tailored pants with a crease. Khaki, twill, and
        corduroy are good fabric choices for business casual but stay away from denim and heavy cotton materials. Pants
        and suits made from wool and wool blends are good standard business attire and work for all seasons. Try to avoid
        synthetic fabrics like rayon and polyester blends which lack quality and can wrinkle.

        \n\n\nMake sure pants are clean, pressed, and wrinkle-free. The hem should cover the ankle but not drape to the
        floor. Even if you have a lovely figure, stay away from pants that are too tight.

        \n\n\nThe first rule is, don’t show cleavage. Blouses should be tailored and coordinate with the rest of your outfit.
        Fine-gauge knit shells are fine but make sure the top is not see-through or too form-fitting.
    </string>


    <string name="womens_casual_outfit">The phrase casual and cute signals to me that the look took less than five minutes to put together.

        \n\n\nFirst you will need jeans because they go with everything. Second, you will need a v-neck or crewneck tee of
        your choice.

        \n\n\nTo take this plain outfit from drab to fab, focus on the outerwear: Cover up with a blazer for
        a hint of sophistication and, if your outfit is lacking color, add in a bright pair of earrings or floral
        boots.The beauty of this ensemble is that it combines all your basic pieces together to form a fresh new look.
    </string>

    <string name="womens_modern_outfit">Versatile, stylish and surprisingly flattering, no matter what your size. Wear it to the knee (or slightly
        shorter if worn with black tights), and make sure it has a little stretch and some draping but is not tight.
        Pair with black tights and booties, or patent-leather pumps for night. Do not wear a flat shoe, but a mid-heel
        or high-heel pump, wedge shoe or boots. (Here is a video about how to shop for shoes that are both stylish and
        sensible.)


        \n\n\nTIP: A black jacket could look severe with this skirt, instead, balance the look with a long tank and a
        cropped multicolored jacket. The best-fitting pencil skirts I have found are from Diane von Furstenberg,
        Michael Kors and Tahari in prices starting at about $120, but you can shop around.
    </string>

    <string name="womens_street_outfit">This is another popular and cool direction of casual style, which is, indeed, perfect in its thoroughness.
        Here you have absolutely no boundaries or limitations and have the free choice of vibes and ways of
        self-expression instead. The most important thing is not to forget about the proportions of delicacy for the
        effortless looks.
    </string>


    <string name="boys_casual_outfit">Why you will love it

        \n\n\nYour kids feet grow so fast, it feels like you are constantly on the lookout for sturdy
        kicks. You can choose from a wide range of Nike and Converse sneakers for kids (new styles
        are added every week). Simply swap them out and return the old pair. It is a great way to budget for shoes over the course of a year, and since every
        box comes with a prepaid envelope, you can also send back as many old pairs as you like for donation or recycling.

        \n\nAges: from sizes 4c to 7y.
    </string>

    <string name="boys_modern_outfit">How it works

        \n\n\nSimply pick your style from various personality types, the trendsetter, the sporty superstar,
        the classic fantastic and more. Then, you will receive six mix-and-match items. If you want to keep everything
        and returns are totally free. You can also change your style preference or cancel at any time. Sounds like a
        super deal to us.

        \n\nAges: 5-12
    </string>

    <string name="boys_street_outfit">Why You will Love It

		\n\n\nKidbox keeps kids top of mind. With a goal of clothing one million children in need, for every complete
		purchased, the company will donate clothes through their partnership with Delivering Good, a non-profit
		dedicated to collecting and distributing new clothing to children in need throughout the U.S.

		\n\nAges: Boys 2-14
    </string>


    <string name="girls_casual_outfit">Why You will Love It

		\n\n\nRockets of Awesome taps into your buying history and preferences to create an ultra-customized shopping
		experience. The more you shop, the more tailored the selections become.

		\n\nAges: Girls 2-14.
    </string>


    <string name="girls_modern_outfit">Why You will Love It

		\n\n\nYou can choose the option that best fits your needs and budget. Each box is different and filled with
		off-the-beaten-path pieces from more than 100 different brands that you wont find in the average retail store.

		\n\nAges: Boys and girls 0-6
    </string>


    <string name="girls_street_outfit">Why You will Love It

		\n\n\nCustomizable to fit your needs, choose to receive your boxes four or eight times a year or try a one-time
		trial box. Each box includes fun extras like a coloring sheet and whimsical iron-on patches.

		\n\nAges: Girls 3-12
    </string>


</resources>